(function () {
  quizzy.data = [
    {  id        : 1
      , question : "question1"
      , answer   : "answer1"
    },
    {  id        : 2
      , question : "question2"  
      , answer   : "answer2"
    },
    {  id        : 3
      , question : "question3"
      , answer   : "answer3"
//  },
//  {  id        : 4
//    , question : "question4"
//    , answer   : "answer4"
//  },
//  {  id        : 5
//    , question : "question5"
//    , answer   : "answer5"
//  },
//  {  id        : 6
//    , question : "question6"
//    , answer   : "answer6"
//  },
//  {  id        : 7
//    , question : "question7"
//    , answer   : "answer7"
//  },
//  {  id        : 8
//    , question : "question8"
//    , answer   : "answer8"
//  },
//  {  id        : 9
//    , question : "question9"
//    , answer   : "answer9"
//  },
//  {  id        : 10
//    , question : "question10"
//    , answer   : "answer10"
    }
  ];
})();
